>> Jem Young: 在此部分中，我们将讨论 HTTP。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: In this section,
we're gonna discuss HTTP.
它可能是其他非安全的部分之一
And it's probably one of the longer
sections of other than security,
因为安全的重要性和 HTTP 是重要的。
because security's important and
HTTP is important.
作为 UI 开发者，我们对底层的挖掘程度感到惊讶。
It's surprising as UI developers how
little we kind of dig into the underlying
把我们所有的密码都转换了
protocol of the thing that's
transforming all of our code.
我的意思是， [ LAUGH] ，我们确实写了超文本标记。
I mean, [LAUGH] we literally
write hypertext markup.
这就是其中的一个方法
And this is one of the ways, or
这就是超文本传输通过因特网传输的方式。
this is the way that hypertext gets
transferred over the Internet.
但我们从来没花过很多时间思考它是如何工作的
But we never spent a lot of time
thinking about, how it's working or
为什么要工作
why it's working?
在我看来要成为一个优秀的全职工程师
So in my mind,
to be a good full stack engineer,
你得明白这个协议是什么
you have to understand
what this protocol is.
就像所有在 P 中结束的其他东西一样，这意味着它是一种协议。
And like everything else that ends in a P,
it means it's a protocol.
[ LAUGH]  是什么 ?
[LAUGH] So what is HTTP?
>> Jem Young: 没有错误的答案。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: There are no wrong answers.
如果你还没弄明白就扔个东西吧
If you haven't figured that out,
just throw something out, yeah?
>> 扬声器 2: 超文本传输协议。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: HyperText
Transport Protocol.
>> Jem Young: 这很好。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: That's pretty good.
你看到下一张幻灯片了吗
Did you look at the next slide?
>> 扬声器 2: 否。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No.
>> Jem Young: 对，对，你是绝对正确的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Right, yes,
you're absolutely right.
超文本传输协议。
HyperText Transport Protocol.
但除了这个定义之外，它到底是什么呢 ?
But what is it really,
besides that definition?
>> 演讲者 2: 这是一个标准吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's a standard?
>> Jem Young: 是的，这东西携带着我们的代码。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah,
it's this thing that carries our code.
它定义代码如何从服务器移动到客户端。
It defines how the code moves
from the server to our client.
更重要的是如何解密
And how to decrypt that, more importantly.
HTTP 通过 TCP 运行。
And HTTP runs over TCP.
我们谈了一些关于 TCP 和 IP 以及 UDP 和所有 P的问题。
And we talked a bit about TCP and
IP and UDP and all the Ps.
但我们最关心的是 HTTP 。
But HTTP's really the one
we care most about.
因为作为一个 UI 工程师，甚至是一个完整的堆工程师，
Because as a UI engineer, or
even a full stack engineer,
你不关心 TCP的事
you don't care that much about TCP.
你知道的
You know that it works.
你知道有个标准组织他们都同意如果我送你
You know that there's a standards body,
that they all agreed that if I send you
信息包与 TCP 协议，传输控制协议，
a packet of information with the TCP
protocol, Transmission Control Protocol,
你知道怎么破译的
you know how to decode that.
但 HTTP 是真的，数据是由它组成的。
But HTTP is really,
it's what the data is comprised of.
因此，包会合并 HTTP 数据，然后对其进行解码。
So a packet wraps HTTP data and
then we decode that.
浏览器都知道解码，他们会说这种共同语言。
And the browser's all know to decode,
they speak this common language.
>> Jem Young: HTTP 的模型是请求和响应，类似于 TCP。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: The model for HTTP is
request and response, much like TCP.
像我们所说的 UDP 或 ICMP一样
Versus something,
like we talked about UDP or ICMP.
这些只是广播的信息包。
Those are just packets
that are broadcasting.
这一问题涉及到请求和响应。
This one cares about request and response.
这是整个 HTTP 模型。
That's the entire model of HTTP.
请求和响应。
The request and response.
我们会去调查的
And we'll dig into that.
>> Jem Young: HTTP 请求实际上类似于以下内容 :
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: An HTTP request
actually looks something like this,
以及数据有效内容。
along with the data payload.
但主要的是，我们看到这里有几个关键部分。
But mainly, we see a few key parts here.
我们看到 GET ，所以方法。
We see the GET, so the method.
然后我们看到一堆头头
Then we see a bunch of headers.
然后就会有一个数据有效载荷。
And then somewhere in there
will be a data payload.
如果我给你看这个并且没有告诉你是 HTTP的，这很有趣。
And it's funny if I showed you this and
didn't tell you it was HTTP.
您可能猜测这是 HTTP 图的外观。
You could probably guess this is
what an HTTP diagram looks like.
但我们从不考虑
But we never think about,
实际结构的细分情况是什么 ?
what is the breakdown of
the actual structure what HTTP is?